netwidedirectory.com 2011-02-02

# Net Wide Directory

Net Wide Directory understands that privacy online is important to users of the Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs Net Wide Directory privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by Net Wide Directory. 

**"Personally Identifiable Information"** refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual. 

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?**  
Net Wide Directory may collect basic user profile information from all Visitors. Net Wide Directory collects the following additional information from Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell. 

**What organizations are collecting the information?**  
In addition to Net Wide Directory direct collection of information, third party service vendors who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect this information from Net Wide Directory Visitors and Authorized Customers. Net Wide Directory does not control how these third parties use such information, but does ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them. 

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  
Net Wide Directory uses Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. Net Wide Directory may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. Net Wide Directory may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information. 

**With whom may the information may be shared?**  
Net Wide Directory may share aggregated information about Visitors, including the demographics of Visitors and Authorized Customers, with affiliated agencies and third party vendors. Net Wide Directory also offers the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by Net Wide Directory or by any agency acting on Net Wide Directory behalf. 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by Net Wide Directory is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of Net Wide Directory except for use as indicated above. 

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?** Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting Net Wide Directory. 

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. Net Wide Directory uses Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of Visitors and the services they select. Net Wide Directory also uses Cookies for security purposes to protect Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 10 minutes, Net Wide Directory will automatically log the Authorized Customer off. 

**How does Net Wide Directory use login information?**  
Net Wide Directory uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information. 

**What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?** Net Wide Directory has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors. Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility. Net Wide Directory privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information. Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law: Net Wide Directory will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. Net Wide Directory will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of Visitors and Authorized Customers. 

**How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**  
All of Net Wide Directory employees are familiar with Net Wide Directory security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. Net Wide Directory audits its security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While Net Wide Directory takes commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and Net Wide Directory cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place. Net Wide Directory will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences. 

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**  
Net Wide Directory will let Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to the privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if Net Wide Directory is changing the privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, Net Wide Directory will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure. 

**Links:**  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. Net Wide Directory encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ.
